[both hands] place blue and light green blocks side-by-side
[right hand] place red block iin center of blue and green blocks
[both hands] arrange purple, green, and light green blocks
[right hand] place cream block in center
[right hand] place red block on cream block
[right hand] place green block on red block
[both hands] place light green, purple, and yellow blocks around base
[left hand] place cream block on yellow block, next to red block
[right hand] stack light blue and yellow blocks on center column
[right hand] stack blue and light blue blocks on top
[right hand] stack light blue and yellow blocks on top
[right hand] stack blue and cream blocks on top
[right hand] stack green block on top
[right hand] place final light blue block on top